# Pablo Kogan

Full-Stack Developer - Project Leader

English CV | Español CV



#### **About me**

Full-Stack Developer with experience +20 years in developing innovative solutions, leading teams, and knowledge transfer. Additionally, I work as a teacher and manage extension, research, and innovation projects at the National University of Comahue. I am seeking new development challenges that provide tools to improve society and industry.

# Personal

Pablo Kogan nationality: Argentina 1980

#### Areas of specialization

Full-Stack Developer · TDD CI/CD · DataData Analytics and Modeling  $\cdot$  PHP  $\cdot$  JS · Python · Docker · Linux

#### Other Skills

Team leadership. Very proactive with self learning and self managment skills. Ability to work on teams, learn and teach.

### Interests

Free Software / AI / Electoral System / Learning Platform



# Work Experience

2014-present Full-Stack developer - Project Leader - IT Manager

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén 9

Project Management, Project Architect, Software development in learning platform and electoral system. Manage extension, research, and innova-

tion projects.

2010-present Full-Stack developer - Dada Scientist - Generative AI

Freelance - cortitoyalpie · Neuquén 💡

Software development of Oil&Gas | Games | Learning solutions. Data Sci-

entist of Electoral System. Maching Learning in Generative Al.

2007-2010

Full-Stack developer - Project leader - IT Manager

ciar SA · Neuguén 💡

Software development of GIS to Oil&Gas solutions.

2005-present **Associate Professor** 

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén 9

Teacher in Programming and Computer Theory Departments for Computer Science Bachelor Degree.



# **LANGUAGES**

**Spanish English** 

mother

# DEVELOPMENT AND **PUBLICATIONS**

Competir+motivar+hornero= aprender hornero

programación, in: TE&ET 2016.

Gukena: escrutinio descentralizado gukena

para voto ponderado, in: JAIIO 2018.

Digital Certificate Management. wene

# Programming

html, css javascript

PHP

python

bash

sql

# **DEGREES**

2020-present **Master in Computer Science** 

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuguén 9

2015-present

Master in Science, Technology and Innovation

Universidad Nacional de Río Negro · Bariloche 🖓



1999-2006

**Bachelor in Computer Science** 

Universidad Nacional del Comahue · Neuquén ?

